[Music] I have it I have it
[音乐]我有我有
questioned if in the relationship I already tell him not to make mistakes again and less with
被问到在恋爱关系中我是否已经告诉过他不要再犯错误了
someone like you who treats me but in a sad situation without interest where you
像你这样对待我的人，但是我却在没有兴趣的情况下悲伤
you looked for it in my heart it does not reach you it is looking for I have and I have a new boyfriend who
你在我心中寻找它，它没有到达你，它在寻找我，我有一个新的男朋友，
I spent stamped to pass the time campaign do not look for me that is that no
我花了很多时间来打发时间，不要找我，那是不
nothing left chain dad dad
一无所有链爸爸爸爸
I do not have what leads me to the crisis, beautiful, the chain is very much there is nothing
我没有什么让我陷入危机的美丽，连锁店非常多，一无所有
you see suffocate settings and vilo is already peeling in the banana you had a
您会看到令人窒息的设置，并且已经在香蕉中剥落了vilo
queen in front but did not evade here, demand is served and you and the
皇后在前，但没有回避这里的需求得到满足，您和
children but toys with the account I die I want your stones and the beatles are
孩子，但有我要死的帐户的玩具，我想要你的石头和甲壳虫
[ __ ] break we close the bars for me we have
搞砸了休息，我们为我关闭酒吧
Now I have everything I had, give me the dry and the friends who advise you not to
现在，我拥有了所有的一切，请给我干，并建议您不要的朋友
write to me and I have a partner is full all this is here when queuing
给我写信，我有一个伴侣很饱，排队时都在这里
I want to deny everything for me, I understood them, we are wrong without you and now my
我想为我否认一切，我理解他们，没有你，我们错了，现在我
ass hank rhon I compose do not look for me is that
我写的屁股汉克·罗恩不要找我的是
here there is nothing left nothing to do
这里什么也没事做
[Music] has no call to discuss ground djs or
[音乐]没有通话讨论地面DJ或
I usually love that music day and I usually
我通常喜欢那个音乐日，我通常
But be careful because we started, you know, you stayed active that the layer and
但是请注意，因为我们开始保持活跃，因此该层和
now I have another and richer it fits me so much it tastes bitter and richer and softer already
现在我又有另一个更丰富的味道，非常适合我，它已经尝起来又苦又富
I told you 'no the baby revealed herself I don't love you last Tuesday she stayed no longer
我告诉过你'不，婴儿露面了，我不爱你，上个星期二，她不再住了
I have time I no longer have a watch now I'm going down
我有时间我不再有手表了，现在我要走了
when I want to cry baby and now everyone cries has a replacement
当我想哭泣的宝贝，现在每个人都哭了，有一个替代品
they cry in it now cry he wants a house and now I have to move because
他们哭了，现在哭了，他想要一间房子，现在我必须搬家，因为
megas of ram pam pam pam pam don't look for me either, there's no left here
数以百万计的ram pam pam pam pam也不要找我，这里没有剩下
nothing nothing at all I need so much for a while I don't have another has to
一无所有一无所有我有那么一阵子无须
the record label dj ground or about what that music I love day and about the little
唱片公司dj或我喜欢的音乐以及关于小音乐的信息
ground why
为何原因
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]